<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Stats Site</title>
    <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Stats Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://naive-betty.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Descriptive statistics for exploring data Learning Objectives Understanding the basics of descriptive statistics and its tools Getting familiar with important principles for visualizing information Ability to apply knowledge and understand descriptive statistics of real data You can summarize data in two ways:
Using nummerical summaries. Using pictures. Vizualising data is preferable not just because most people rather look at pictures than at numbers, but it can also reveal trends that are not obvious instantanously, especially when looking at a large data set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matplotlib</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/matplotlib/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/matplotlib/</guid>
      <description>Matplotlib is a plotting library. In this section give a brief introduction to the matplotlib.pyplot module.
Installation Install via pip:
pip install matplotlib Import As Matplotlib builds on the NumPy library, you have to import both.
import numpy as np import matplotlib.pyplot as plt Create a basic plot # Compute the x and y coordinates for points on a sine curve x = np.arange(0, 3 * np.pi, 0.1) y = np.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NumPy Library Intro</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/numpy-library-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/numpy-library-intro/</guid>
      <description>Intro to NumPy Python Library Numpy official documentation:
The fundamental package for scientific computing with Python.
NumPy doesn’t depend on any other Python packages, however, it does depend on an accelerated linear algebra library - typically Intel MKL or OpenBLAS. Users don’t have to worry about installing those
For the basics intro see: https://numpy.org/devdocs/user/quickstart.html
Installation Via conda or pip:
pip install numpy Import Customary way to import:
import numpy as np Numpy Arrays A NumPy array is a grid of values, all of the same type, and is indexed by a tuple of nonnegative integers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scipy Library</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/scipy_library/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/scipy_library/</guid>
      <description>Intro to SciPy Library https://scipy.org/
is an open-source software for mathematics, science, and engineering.
SciPy docs
The SciPy library builds on the NymPy&amp;rsquo;s library multidimentional arrays and offers a large number of functions that operate on them.
It is useful for different types of scientific and engineering applications.
The SciPy.stats sub-library. Within the .stats sub-library, we see functions for continuous and discreet distributions, descriptive statistics, and also statistical test such as T-test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver for Slaves</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/silver-for-slaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/python/silver-for-slaves/</guid>
      <description>Visit to the silver for slaves exhibition A visit to the Silver for Slaves exhibition at the Silesian Museum in Gorlitz has impressed me and inspired to look further into the data I found overthere. The price that would be paid for certain items such as live stock, artefacts or slaves is something th
To see a price of foodstuffs, livestock and artefacts alongside prices for a slave is shocking. It is even more shocking to see how the price of a slave compares to other prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Univariate Data</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/univariate-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/univariate-data/</guid>
      <description>Univariate data Qualitative (categorical) data pie chart or dot plot - Comparison is easier on the dot plot - Pie chart is better at showing the percentage of the total that the category represents Problems with pie charts - Very small slices might overlap - it is hard to compare slices without proper labeling: it is easier to compare when looking at a bar chart
Pie Chart, Bar Graph, Table Quantitative data Quantitative(numbers): bar chart and histogram</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/hidden/</guid>
      <description>This page is hidden in menu Latent te facies Lorem markdownum arma ignoscas vocavit quoque ille texit mandata mentis ultimus, frementes, qui in vel. Hippotades Peleus pennas conscia cuiquam Caeneus quas.
Pater demittere evincitque reddunt Maxime adhuc pressit huc Danaas quid freta Soror ego Luctus linguam saxa ultroque prior Tatiumque inquit Saepe liquitur subita superata dederat Anius sudor </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
