<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistics introduction on My Stats Site</title>
    <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistics introduction on My Stats Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Descriptive statistics for exploring data Learning Objectives Understanding the basics of descriptive statistics and its tools Getting familiar with important principles for visualizing information Ability to apply knowledge and understand descriptive statistics of real data You can summarize data in two ways:
Using nummerical summaries. Using pictures. Vizualising data is preferable not just because most people rather look at pictures than at numbers, but it can also reveal trends that are not obvious instantanously, especially when looking at a large data set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Univariate Data</title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/univariate-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/univariate-data/</guid>
      <description>Univariate data Qualitative (categorical) data pie chart or dot plot - Comparison is easier on the dot plot - Pie chart is better at showing the percentage of the total that the category represents Problems with pie charts - Very small slices might overlap - it is hard to compare slices without proper labeling: it is easier to compare when looking at a bar chart
Pie Chart, Bar Graph, Table Quantitative data Quantitative(numbers): bar chart and histogram</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naive-betty.netlify.app/docs/example/hidden/</guid>
      <description>This page is hidden in menu Latent te facies Lorem markdownum arma ignoscas vocavit quoque ille texit mandata mentis ultimus, frementes, qui in vel. Hippotades Peleus pennas conscia cuiquam Caeneus quas.
Pater demittere evincitque reddunt Maxime adhuc pressit huc Danaas quid freta Soror ego Luctus linguam saxa ultroque prior Tatiumque inquit Saepe liquitur subita superata dederat Anius sudor </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
